A Guide to the C. F. Sugg papers, 1882-1922
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
C. F. Sugg papers, 1882-1922
The Library of Virginia
51506
.225 cu. ft. and 1 box
C. F. Sugg
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Eve Love of Hollywood, Maryland.
Biographical Information
Charles Frederick Sugg was born in Enfield, North Carolina, to Phesanton and Lucinda Suggs. As an adult, Sugg moved to Caroline County, Virginia, where he began working in the lumber industry. Sugg married Merrie Pender (1855-1942) of Richmond, Virginia, 13 September 1876, and they had six children. Sugg died in Spotsylvania County, Virginia, 11 December 1933, and was buried in Hollywood Cemetery in Richmond.
Scope and Content
Papers, 1882-1922, of C. F. Sugg (1854-1933) of Caroline County, Virginia, consisting of accounts, correspondence, receipts, and tax records. Accounts and correspondence concern Sugg's personal and business debts. Much of the correspondence regards Sugg's failure to pay his debts and notes. Correspondence also concerns farm property Sugg has on the market.
Contents List
- Conway, Gordon, and Garnett papers, 1890 (Folder 1)
- H. H. George, Jr., letters, 1887 (Folder 2)
- George A. Haynes papers, 1884-1887 (Folder 3)
- Knopf Brothers accounts, 1890, undated (Folder 4)
- A. Lyell papers, 1886-1891 (Folder 5)
- John McNabb correspondence, 1889 (Folder 6)
- Miller and Rhoads accounts and receipts, 1918-1922 (Folder 7)
- W. Washington letters, 1890-1891 (Folder 8)
- Wortham papers, 1882-1885 (Folder 9)
- Doctors (Roderick Dew, Frank C. Pratt, C. S. Webb), 1915-1922 (Folder 10)
- General correspondence, 1882, 1890-1891 (Folder 11)
- General accounts, 1883-1891, 1921, undated (Folder 12)
- Taxes, 1909-1912 (Folder 13)